put lunchbox
put bottle
close washing machine
open bottle
turn on tap
close bottle
shake bottle
open bottle
pour bottle
turn on tap
fill bottle
turn off tap
close bottle
open fridge
put bottle in fridge
grab squash
close fridge
put squash
grab bottle
open bottle
fill bottle
close bottle
shake bottle
put squash
open bottle
pour water
open squash
pour squash
put bottle
close squash
open fridge
put squash
close fridge
fill bottle
turn off tap
close bottle
open fridge
put bottle in fridge
grab bread
grab cheese
grab butter
close fridge
put food
open cupboard
grab plate
close cupboard
move lunchbox
put plate
grab slices of bread
put bread
grab bread
open fridge
put bread
close fridge
open butter
grab knife
turn on water
get butter
spread butter
wipe excess butter
put lid on butter
open up cheese
turn on tap
slice cheese
put cheese on bread
close sandwich
cut sandwich
test water
grab washing up liquid
pour washing up liquid
put washing up liquid
move tap
open lunchbox
tip out lunchbox
put slices in lunchbox
close lunchbox
put cheese in bag
grab butter
open fridge
put butter in fridge
put cheese in fridge
grab lunchbox
put lunchbox in fridge
close fridge
grab bowl
grab spoon
grab spatula
grab knives and forks
grab saucepan
put saucepan
grab plate
grab sponge
wash plate
put plate
grab plate
wash plate
put plate on rack
put plate in rack
grab bowl
wash bowl
put bowl in rack
grab bowl
wash bowl
put bowl
grab knife
wash knife
put knife in rack
grab knife
wash knife
grab spoon and spatula
grab cutting board
put mess in bin
wipe cutting board
continue washing cutting board
put cutting board in rack
grab measuring cup
wash measuring cup
put measuring cup in rack
grab saucepan
grab sponge
put sponge
grab lid
wash lid
put lid in rack
grab plate
put knife
wash plate
put plate
wash saucepan
continue washing saucepan
put saucepan
wash spatula?
wash spoon
put spoon
wash spatula
put spatula*
wash cutlery
put cutlery
wash spoon
put spoon
wash knife
put knife
wash fork
put fork
clean side
wipe hob
clean hob
put in bin
pour water
turn on tap
rinse bowl
put sponge
wash hands
rinse bowl
rinse sink
dry hands
get kitchen towel
dry side
dry hob
put kitchen towel in bin
turn off tap
put plug
put bowl
turn on tap
clean side
turn off tap
wash
dry hands